Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
(Episode 14)
(الحلقة 14)
There's something I want to tell you.
هناك شيء أريد أن أخبرك به.
Da Huan.
دا هوان.
So...
لذا...
you're my brother, Da Xi?
أنت أخي دا شي؟
You're Tong Sheng from Xuebao Group?
هل أنت تونغ شنغ من مجموعة Xuebao؟
After the accident,
بعد الحادث،
you were the one who lived with me.
أنت من كنت تعيش معي.
Then...
ثم...
it became Da Xi?
أصبح دا شي؟
And then...
وثم...
you again.
انت مرة أخرى.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I came here to find out...
لقد جئت إلى هنا لمعرفة...
the truth about my family,
الحقيقة حول عائلتي،
but I didn't expect you...
ولكنني لم أتوقعك...
to be braver than I imagined.
أن أكون أكثر شجاعة مما كنت أتخيل.
No wonder.
لا عجب.
Not only can you speak French, but you also know everything.
ليس فقط أنك تستطيع التحدث باللغة الفرنسية، بل أنت تعرف كل شيء أيضًا.
Also...
أيضًا...
You two went through a series of indescribable events.
لقد مررتم بسلسلة من الأحداث التي لا يمكن وصفها.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Da Xi.
من شي.
It's me. Are you all right?
أنا، هل أنت بخير؟
Where's Tong Sheng?
أين تونغ شنغ؟
He left.
لقد غادر.
He left?
هل غادر؟
Why did he leave?
لماذا ترك؟
He doesn't even live here.
إنه لا يعيش هنا حتى.
So why is he here?
فلماذا هو هنا؟
Do you want him to take care of you?
هل تريد منه أن يهتم بك؟
No.
لا.
Do you miss him?
هل تفتقدينه؟
Why don't you just tell me?
لماذا لا تخبرني فقط؟
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
ألم أخبرك بالأمس؟
I wanted you to talk to me alone.
أردت منك أن تتحدث معي على انفراد.
I'm already sick and you're still teasing me.
أنا مريض بالفعل وأنت لا تزال تمزح معي.
Your act isn't convincing at all.
إن فعلك غير مقنع على الإطلاق.
You've known all along that Da Xi isn't really your brother.
لقد كنت تعلم طوال الوقت أن دا شي ليس أخاك حقًا.
Da Xi...
من شي...
was brought home from an orphanage by my mom when I was a child.
تم إحضاره إلى المنزل من دار الأيتام بواسطة والدتي عندما كنت طفلاً.
I've always treated him as my real brother.
لقد تعاملت معه دائمًا كأخي الحقيقي.
But he's actually my brother.
لكن في الحقيقة هو أخي.
I can't believe Da Xi...
لا أستطيع أن أصدق دا شي...
is the Tong family's lost child.
هو الطفل المفقود لعائلة تونغ.
I only found out recently.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك مؤخرًا.
My dad has been secretly searching for him...
لقد كان والدي يبحث عنه سراً...
and this was kept from both me and Tong An.
وقد تم إخفاء هذا الأمر عني وعن تونغ آن.
So now,
لذا الآن،
can you stop...
هل يمكنك التوقف...
Wanqi and Xuebao's collaboration?
تعاون Wanqi وXuebao؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll take care of the rest.
سأعتني بالباقي.
Although I haven't fully regained my memory,
على الرغم من أنني لم أستعد ذاكرتي بالكامل،
but I promise...
ولكنني أعدك...
I won't let what happened yesterday happen again.
لن أسمح لما حدث بالأمس أن يحدث مرة أخرى.
And I'll never let anyone bully you again.
ولن اسمح لأحد أن يتنمر عليك مرة أخرى.
But you have to promise me too.
ولكن عليك أن تعدني أيضاً.
No matter what happens in the future,
بغض النظر عما يحدث في المستقبل،
don't rush into things first.
لا تتسرع في الأمور أولاً.
Remember.
يتذكر.
You still have me.
لا زلت تملكني.
I've already sent someone...
لقد أرسلت شخصًا بالفعل...
to deal with Bai Yu Chen.
للتعامل مع باي يو تشن.
Deal with him? How?
التعامل معه؟ كيف؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It's nothing more than giving him what he deserves.
إنه ليس شيئًا أكثر من إعطائه ما يستحقه.
His affairs have been made public...
لقد أصبحت شؤونه علنية...
and his reputation should be in ruins by now.
ويجب أن تكون سمعته في حالة خراب الآن.
Have a good rest.
خذ قسطا جيدا من الراحة.
Don't worry about the rest.
لا تقلق بشأن الباقي.
Da Xi.
من شي.
Tong Sheng.
تونغ شنغ.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Get some rest.
احصل على بعض الراحة.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
Dad.
أب.
Why did you put the merger on hold?
لماذا أوقفتم عملية الدمج؟
With all the commotion you caused at the press conference,
مع كل الضجة التي أحدثتها في المؤتمر الصحفي،
I have to think it over again.
يجب علي أن أفكر في الأمر مرة أخرى.
Also,
أيضًا،
the new legal advisor you hired...
المستشار القانوني الجديد الذي قمت بتعيينه...
has made a complete mess.
لقد أحدث فوضى كاملة.
There was even scandalous news at the press conference.
وكان هناك أيضًا أخبار فاضحة في المؤتمر الصحفي.
How is this acceptable?
كيف يكون هذا مقبولا؟
I need to reassess everything,
أحتاج إلى إعادة تقييم كل شيء،
so the project is on hold.
لذلك تم تعليق المشروع.
- Dad, it's not like that. - By the way,
- أبي، الأمر ليس كذلك. - بالمناسبة،
how is Tong Sheng recovering?
كيف يتعافى تونغ شنغ؟
I plan to let him take over.
أخطط للسماح له بتولي المسؤولية.
He's doing well.
إنه بخير.
There's no conflict between you two, right?
لا يوجد صراع بينكما، أليس كذلك؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Brothers have to look out...
يجب على الإخوة أن ينتبهوا...
for each other in many ways.
لبعضنا البعض في كثير من النواحي.
You need to understand that.
يجب عليك أن تفهم ذلك.
That's for sure.
هذا مؤكد.
Okay, that's all.
حسنا، هذا كل شيء.
Mr. Tong.
السيد تونغ.
You forced me to do this.
لقد أجبرتني على فعل هذا.
Are you home?
هل انت في المنزل؟
I bought medicine.
لقد اشتريت الدواء.
I'm almost home.
أنا تقريبا وصلت إلى المنزل.
I want to eat canned fruit.
أريد أن آكل الفاكهة المعلبة.
I'll go buy it now.
سأذهب لشرائه الآن.
Never mind. Buy it next time.
لا بأس، اشتريه في المرة القادمة.
Come back soon.
عد قريبا.
Tong Sheng, are you okay?
تونغ شنغ، هل أنت بخير؟
Tong Sheng.
تونغ شنغ.
I think...
أظن...
I remember everything.
انا أتذكر كل شيء.
Tong Sheng.
تونغ شنغ.
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
Everything is clear now.
كل شيء واضح الآن.
Dad has rushed back from abroad too.
لقد عاد الأب مسرعًا من الخارج أيضًا.
Chang Ming.
تشانغ مينغ.
Tell me about it.
أخبرني عن ذلك.
Dad, I don't know what to say.
أبي لا أعرف ماذا أقول.
Chang Ming.
تشانغ مينغ.
How about I start for you?
ماذا عن أن أبدأ لك؟
Let's begin with how Tong Sheng's car...
دعونا نبدأ مع كيفية سيارة تونغ شنغ...
was tampered with.
تم العبث بها.
No, Dad.
لا يا أبي.
It was my subordinate who did it.
لقد كان مرؤوسي هو من فعل ذلك.
I just found out too.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك للتو أيضًا.
He has already fled abroad.
لقد فر بالفعل إلى الخارج.
I'm planning to go overseas myself to bring him back...
أخطط للسفر إلى الخارج بنفسي لإعادته...
and confront him face-to-face.
وواجهه وجهاً لوجه.
Dad, I honestly didn't know about this.
أبي، أنا بصراحة لم أكن أعلم بهذا.
I really didn't know.
لم أكن أعلم حقا.
You have to believe me.
يجب عليك أن تصدقني.
Make it quick.
اجعلها سريعة.
I don't want to see Tong Sheng after tomorrow.
لا أريد رؤية تونغ شنغ بعد الغد.
- Do you understand? - Yes.
- هل فهمت؟ - نعم.
Keep an eye on Tong Sheng.
ابقي عينك على تونغ شنغ.
If he shows any signs of regaining his memory,
إذا أظهر أي علامات على استعادة ذاكرته،
notify me immediately.
أعلمني على الفور.
- Yes. - Chang Ming.
- نعم. - تشانغ مينغ.
Let's drop the act and keep some dignity.
دعونا نتوقف عن هذا الفعل ونحتفظ ببعض الكرامة.
Chang Ming.
تشانغ مينغ.
After Tong Sheng's accident,
بعد حادث تونغ شنغ،
I asked Tong An to investigate the whole thing.
طلبت من تونغ آن التحقيق في الأمر برمته.
Later, you met Jin Da Xi at the company.
وفي وقت لاحق، التقيت بجين دا شي في الشركة.
You manipulated him...
لقد تلاعبت به...
into signing a contract that harmed the company's interests,
إلى توقيع عقد يضر بمصالح الشركة،
forcing me to dismiss him.
أجبرني على طرده.
That way, you could take over the company...
بهذه الطريقة، يمكنك الاستحواذ على الشركة...
and collude with Wanqi Group.
والتواطؤ مع مجموعة وانكي.
Did I leave anything out?
هل تركت شيئا؟
Tong Sheng.
تونغ شنغ.
You have to understand me.
عليك أن تفهمني.
From the moment Jin Da Xi entered our home,
منذ اللحظة التي دخل فيها جين دا شي إلى منزلنا،
Tong An realized...
أدركت تونغ آن...
we had mistaken him for you.
لقد أخطأنا في اعتباره لك.
However, he advised me not to expose Jin Da Xi...
ولكنه نصحني بعدم فضح جين دا شي...
nor to rush into acknowledging him.
ولا التسرع في الاعتراف به.
We did this...
لقد فعلنا هذا...
to give you another chance.
لأمنحك فرصة أخرى.
I kept waiting for you to stop...
كنت أنتظر منك أن تتوقف...
and willingly admit your mistakes.
واعترف بأخطائك طوعا.
Tong An.
تونغ آن.
You really hid it well.
لقد أخفيته جيدًا حقًا.
In the end, I could never outmatch the Tong family.
في النهاية، لم أتمكن أبدًا من التفوق على عائلة تونغ.
Chang Ming.
تشانغ مينغ.
I've always treated you like my own brother,
لقد تعاملت معك دائمًا كما لو كنت أخي،
just like Tong An.
تمامًا مثل تونغ آن.
We're all one family.
نحن جميعا عائلة واحدة.
I never expected you to be so cruel.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن تكون قاسيًا إلى هذه الدرجة.